

1800 102 2558 | +91 9818882211







Jump to Section V

Last Active: Jan-Mar 2021

2021 Last Modified: Jan-Mar 2021

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills | Work Authorization

Summary

Specialized in Technology Leadership roles as 'Director/Head of Product Engineering', Director/Head of HR Technology at Barclays, Director Technology at Scientific Games, Director Technology at Bally Tech. Expertise in Enterprise Software development, Engineering, Innovation, Digital, Turnaround business strategies in Banking Financial, Gaming Systems, Supply Chain, Manufacturing & Publishing domain. Delivered 80+ products & transformed systems involving Web technologies, Saas, Big Data, Mobile, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Al, Cloud, Distributed, Chat-bots, Mcro Services, Automation. Setup 200+ India team and managed 175+ across geographies with diverse technologies in Product Development, Architecture, Dev-Ops, Agile Scrum, Ul/UX, QA Automation, PM, Tech Docs & Support. Passionate in driving Innovation, Ideas, Patents into Product and embed as part of team culture. Drive for Strategic Vision, Technology Transformation, Increased revenue, Digital Strategy and Execution.

Work Experience

codeMantra as Director & Head of Product Engineering -IT Feb 2020 to Till Date

Head of Product Engineering, Managing Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Micro-Services, AWS SaaS products with a team of 80+ members in Development, Architecture, QA, Support & Implementation.

Barclays as Director Technology Sep 2018 to Jul 2019

Heading Technology team of 150+ employees across Chennai and Pune locations. Develop and implement Product Development Strategy and road maps. Build high-performing team and capability in new center and deliver outstanding products & systems.

Scientific Games as Director Technology Aug 2014 to May 2018

Building end to end new product development in Web, Angular JS, Mobile Apps, .NET, Java, Big Data & QA Managed a team of team of 175+ employees. Innovation expert, driving R&D initiatives, DevOps & Agile.

Bally Technologies as Director Technology Jun 2006 to Jul 2014

Development head of Internal Systems Product Development Group & Enterprise HR Systems End-to-End execution of product developments involving .NET, Angular JS, Mobile, Java, Mddleware.



Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

- Target Technology Services as Senior Software Engineer Mar 2006 to May 2006
- Hewlett-Packard as Software Engineer Sep 2004 to Mar 2006

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Mechanical) from National Engineering College in 2002 $\,$ PG: in 0

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Angular, .NET, Big Data	
JAVA	
Hadoop, Spark	
KAFKA, NoSQL	
MICRO SERVICES	
Oracle EBS	
COGNOS BI	
SAP HR	
mICROSOFT erP	
MICRO SERVICES	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

L	anguage	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
E	English	Proficient	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

US Work Status: Need H1 Visa

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.